Prasad J

Full Stack Developer



in LinkedIn



GitHub



+91 97890 45593



M raghav21prasad@gmail.com



Chennai, India

Full Stack Developer with 4+ years of experience in the field of web development using JavaScript frameworks (Angular 12+, ReactJs, NextJs, NextJs) and C#. A developer who likes to work in a challenging environment to bring out the best solutions.

SKILLS

Programming Languages: JavaScript, TypeScript, C#, HTML, CSS3 and JQuery

JavaScript Frameworks: Angular12+, ReactJs, NextJs, NestJs

Database & Queue: PostgreSQL, MySQL, Azure SQL, Azure Queue

Cloud Technologies: Azure

Methodology: Agile Tools: Git, VS Code

WORK EXPERIENCE

January 2020 - Present **Botminds Inc**

Al Engineer

• Worked in Table AI feature to Identify and extract essential information from table using Angular and JQuery

- Implemented Okta integration for Single Sign On (SSO) with OIDC method using C# and Angular
- Built Auto derivation library a post prediction process where customised logics applied to derive new values
- Developed a dashboard widget where the columns, filters can be customised for analytics using C# and Angular
- Implemented document stage management to keep track of the document's current stage and user using c# and Angular
- Improved product stability and performance to seamlessly load and render documents to provide better user experience
- Worked in developing the SEO friendly enterprise website using NextJs to get maximum reach in marketing campaign

Tata Consultancy Services

June 2018 - December 2019

Mumbai, India

Chennai, India

Assistant System Engineer

- Worked as an R&I Developer in CTO Incubation team to build web applications for Drones and ChatBot creator platform
- Developed UI platform to create, train and interact with AI-powered Chatbots using Angular 7
- Developed backend API's to create hierarchical model for drones to identify objects in a warehouse using Python flask framework

EDUCATION

Rajalakshmi Engineering College

June 2014 - May 2018

Bachelor's of Engineering in ECE - CGPA: 7.8/10

Chennai, India

PROJECTS

Web Based Resume September 2022

Created this resume using ReactJs and downloaded resume as PDF using puppeteer. <u>Live Demo</u>

Vizhithiru App December 2020 - February 2021

 Created an application for logging and escalating complaints in ReactJs to notify the election department about the common issues